Finding aid for Mike Wallace CBS/60 Minutes Papers, 1922-2007
Bentley Historical Library
- 60 Minutes Program Files
  - Viewer Correspondence
    - 1994
      - Mexico and Corruption, aired, May 1994 (Box W2)
      - Nixon, Richard (Retrospective), aired, April 24, 1994 (Box 131)
      - "Pelican Bay" (California prison), aired, June 12, 1994 (Box 131)
      - Streisand, Barbra, aired, June 26, 1994 (Box 131)
      - Swindle (Rip-offs of seniors), aired, July 10, 1994 (Box W2)
      - "Up in Smoke," aired, March 27, 1994 (Box 131)
      - Woodward, Bob, aired, June 5, 1994 (Box 131)
      - Yandle, Joseph, aired February (?), 1994 (Box 131)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 131)
    - 1995
      - Various titles, 20 folders (Box 132)
    - 1997
      - Old Age and Retirement (Box 132)
      - "Traitor or Hero?" (Ward Connerly), aired, November 9, 1997 (Box 132)
    - 2000
      - Kevorkian, Jack (Box 132)
  - Miscellaneous Story Ideas (By Producer)
    - Anderson, Bob, 1993-1996; 4 folders (Box 133)
    - Anderson, Tom, 1996 (Box 133)
    - Bailey, Margaret, 1996 (Box 133)
    - Bergman, Lowell, 1993-1997; 3 folders (Box 133)
    - Bluff, Peter, 1993-1994 (Box 133)
    - Bonin, Richard (Box 133)
    - Bronstein, Scott, 1996 (Box 133)
    - Fine, Paul and Holly, 1990-1996; 2 folders (Box 133)
    - Gallagher, Paul, undated (Box 133)
    - Howard, Josh, 1993-1994 (Box 133)
    - Kim, Ty, 1996 (Box 133)
    - Lando, Barry, 1990-1996; 3 folders (Box 133)
    - Lewis, Chuck, 1988 (Box 133)
    - McClure, Bill, 1993-1995 (Box 133)
    - Miscellaneous, 1993-1995 (Box 133)
    - Rosmarin, Isidore, 1988 (Box 133)
    - Strong, Morgan, 1996 (Box 133)
    - Szechenyi, Chris, 1994 (Box 133)
    - Thompson, Charlie, 2 folders (Box 133)
    - Wood, Terry, 1995 (Box 133)
  - Collected transcripts
    (in binders)
    - 60 Minutes; Highlights; 1956-1963 News Specials/Special Reports; Before CBS News; List of Tapes; Leaders/Entertainers; The Early Years; Newsbeat; Highlights 1963-1989 Producer Credits, 1956-1989 (Box 46)
    - 60 Minutes: Transcripts, A-Z, 5 volumes (Box 46)
    - 60 Minutes: Transcripts: The Reagans (Box 46)
    - 60 Minutes: Transcripts: Vietnam (Box 46)
    - 60 Minutes: Wallace Pieces, ("Show Binder"), 1968-1990 (Box W1)
    - Biography Articles/Interviews (Box 47)
    - CBS Reports/Special Reports Transcripts (Box 47)
    - The Mike Wallace Interview A-Z, 3 volumes (Box 47)
    - The Mike Wallace Interview Selected from the University of Texas at Austin Archives, 1957-58 (Box 47)
- General Files
  The second largest series in the collection is the General Files which date from 1964 to 2006 with a few scattered files dating from as early as 1957. The researcher should note that Mike Wallace had previously donated to the library papers covering his career in television in the 1950s prior to coming to CBS. These papers do not form part of the CBS/60 Minute files described within this finding aid.
  The General Files are a combination of personal and professional materials covering (as indicated) facets of 60 Minutes programming as well as Wallace's other responsibilities within CBS News, notably his work covering the war in Vietnam and political campaigns in the 1960s and 1970s. Included within the General Files are CBS administrative memoranda and expense reports; correspondence with colleagues, friends, and viewers; personal files detailing speech engagements, and documentation of charitable and other professional activities. As mentioned, the General Files before 1980 includes topical files with accumulated information on potential or actual 60 Minutes program segments. After 1980, these files were placed within the Program Files.
  - 1957
    - Edward Bennett Williams Interview, December 14 (Box 52)
  - 1959
    - Topical: Communism: Earl Browder, 1957-1959 (Box 52)
  - 1963
    - Topical: Joseph Valachi Hearings (Box 52)
    - Topical: Philip Wylie Response to Mike Wallace Interview, 1957-1963 (Box 52)
  - 1964
    - * Administrative
      - National Telefilm Associates (breach of contract dispute) (Box 52)
      - Ratings, 1962-1964 (Box 52)
      - Station Lists, 1962-1964 (Box 52)
    - * Personal
      - Speeches/Appearances
        - Travelers Men's Club, Travelers Insurance Company, October 1 (Hartford, CT) (Box 52)
        - New York Society for Clinical Psychiatry, November 12 (New York, NY) (Box 52)
        - Millbrook School, December 4 (Millbrook, NY) (Box 52)
        - Chalmers "Bump" Elliot Tribute, University of Michigan Sports Dinner, December 10 (Box 52)
      - Syracuse University Records Transfer (Box 52)
    - Topical
      - Campaign, 1964
        - Democratic and Republican Headquarters Contact Information (Box 52)
        - Newspaper Contacts (Box 52)
        - "The Press and the Candidates" transcripts, CBS Radio (September to October) (Box 52)
        - Correspondence (Box 52)
        - Arizona (Richard Kleindienst) (Box 52)
        - Arkansas (Winthrop Rockefeller and Orval Faubus) (Box 52)
        - Illinois (Charles Percy and Otto Kerner) (Box 52)
        - Massachusetts (John Volpe and Francis Bellotti) (Box 52)
        - Michigan (George Romney and Neil Staebler) (Box 52)
        - Wisconsin (John Reynolds and Warren Knowles) (Box 52)
        - Democratic Convention Correspondence (Box 52)
        - Republican Convention Correspondence (Box 52)
        - Gubernatorial Races (Box 52)
        - CBS Coverage of Election Procedures and Roles (Box 52)
        - Democratic Convention, State Information (Box 52)
        - CBS Memo, California Republican Presidential Primary (Box 52)
      - Eleanor Roosevelt Memorial Foundation, 1963-1964 (Box 52)
      - Halls-Mills Murder Case (Box 52)
      - Interview Research, 1961-1964 (Box 52)
      - John Birch Society (Box 52)
      - National Klan Association (Box 52)
      - Rothmans of Pall Mall Canada (French Canadian Television Show Action 64) (Box 52)
      - Saturn Rocket Program (Box 52)
      - Tarrytown House (Business Education) (Box 52)
    - Transcripts/Shows
      - "Arrest and Seizure," WCBS-TV Documentary (Box 52)
      - CBS Morning News Script Excerpts, 1963-1964 (Box 52)
      - "Segregation: Northern Style," December 9 (Box 52)
  - 1965
    - Administrative
      - CBS Memos (Box 52)
      - CBS News Internal Releases (Box 52)
      - Expense Reports (Box 52)
      - Foreign Bureaus (Box 52)
      - Memos from Mike Wallace (Box 52)
      - Out-of-Town Bureaus (Box 52)
      - Petty Cash Receipts (Box 52)
      - Ratings
        - Arbitron (Box 52)
        - General (Box 52)
        - Nielsen (Box 52)
      - Transportation (Box 52)
    - Correspondence
      - Miscellaneous (Box 52)
      - Personal (includes some expense reports) (Box 52)
    - * Personal
      - Invitations (Box 52)
      - Phi Epsilon Pi Fraternity (Box 52)
      - Public Relations Committee, United Jewish Appeal (Box 52)
      - Publicity (Box 52)
      - Rodgers and Hammerstein Wing for Experimental Medicine and Cancer Research, Medical School, Hebrew University, 1963-1965 (Box 52)
      - Speeches/Appearances
        - Miscellaneous (Box 52)
        - Letchworth Village, Welfare League, Association for Retarded Children, 1963-1965 (Box 52)
        - Brenda Award Dinner, Atlanta Chapter of Theta Sigma Phi, The Professional Organization for Women in Journalism and Communications and the Atlanta Advertising Institute, April 9 (Atlanta, GA) (Box 52)
        - "Politics, Television, What Next?" Tea Association Mid-Year Meeting, Tea Council of the USA, May 5 (New York, NY) (Box 52)
      - Wide World Lecture Bureau (Box 52)
    - Topical
      - Broadcast Services (Box 52)
      - Gemini 3 (GT-3) Space Mission, March 23 (includes interview transcript) (Box 53)
      - Gemini 4 (GT-4) Space Mission, June (includes transcript) (Box 53)
      - Gemini 5 (GT-5) Space Mission, August 4 (Box 53)
      - Gemini 6 (GT-6) Space Mission, October 25 (Box 53)
      - Gemini 7/6 (GT-7/GT-6) Space Mission, December (Box 53)
      - Inauguration Data, President Lyndon B. Johnson and Vice President Hubert H. Humphrey (Box 53)
      - John V. Lindsay (Box 53)
      - New York Mayoralty Race (Box 53)
      - Political File, 1963-1965 (Box 53)
      - Space Flights, General (Box 53)
      - Malcolm X and Black Muslims (includes interview transcript) (Box 53)
    - Transcripts/Shows
      - "The Apathetic American,", 1964-1965 (Box 53)
      - Biography Series (Box 53)
      - Mike Wallace at Large
        - Audience Mail (Box 53)
        - Novak and Donovan Interview (political reporters) Regarding Barry Goldwater (Box 53)
        - Susan Sontag Interview (Box 53)
        - Morris West Interview Regarding Vietnam, February 3 (Box 53)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 53)
      - Richard Nixon Interview Face the Nation, November 21 (Box 53)
      - Personal Close-up Radio Series (Box 53)
      - "The Responsive Eye," Eye on New York Production, WCBS-TV Documentary, April 20 (Box 53)
  - 1966
    - Administrative
      - CBS Memos (Box 53)
      - Commercial Schedule (Box 53)
      - Expense Reports (Box 53)
      - Memos from Mike Wallace (Box 53)
      - Petty Cash Receipts (Box 53)
      - Ratings (Box 53)
      - Washington Bureau (Box 53)
    - Correspondence
      - A-Z, 2 folders (Box 53)
      - Audience Mail
        - General (Box 53)
        - Morning News Departure (Box 53)
        - Regarding "Civil Rights -- the View from the South" (Box 53)
        - Regarding General Motors "On the Job" Training Program (Box 53)
    - Personal
      - Expenses and Correspondence (Box 53)
      - Invitations (Box 53)
      - Job Applications (Box 53)
      - Publicity (Box 53)
      - University of Michigan Activities, 1965-1966 (Box 54)
    - Topical
      - Apollo Space Program (Box 54)
      - Chicago Riots (Box 54)
      - Elections, General (Box 54)
      - Elections, Governors (Box 54)
      - Father Gommar De Pauw (communism in the church) (Box 54)
      - Gemini 8 Recovery Ship, U.S.S. Boxer (Box 54)
      - Gemini 8 Space Mission (Box 54)
      - Gemini 9 Space Mission (Box 54)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 54)
      - National Conference for New Politics (Box 54)
      - Richard Nixon (includes interview) (Box 54)
      - Surveyor A and Pioneer B Spacecrafts (Box 54)
      - Transit Strike, New York City (Box 54)
      - University of California at Berkeley (Box 54)
      - Vietnam (Box 54)
      - Who Pays for Politics? (Box 54)
    - Transcripts/Shows
      - "The National Drivers Test," May 24, 1966 (Box 54)
      - "Black Power, White Backlash," September 27 (Box 54)
      - Debriefing Series, CBS Radio (Box 54)
      - Face the Nation with Guest Ronald Reagan, October 30 (Box 54)
      - "The National Health Test," Part 1: January 18, Part 2: January 25 (Box 54)
      - "The National Income Tax Test," April 5 (Box 54)
      - Personal Close-up Release Forms (Box 54)
      - Personal Close-up Scripts
        - January (Robert St. John, Julie Christine, Louis Malle and Brigitte Bardot, Mel Torme, Sam Mostel, Jack Carter, Wright Patman, Arthur Schlesinger) (Box 54)
        - February (Thurgood Marshall, Father Gommar De Pauw, Lloyd Hand) (Box 54)
        - March (Joseph Maddy, Jo Collins, Moshe Dayan) (Box 54)
        - April (Michael Wood, John Coleman Bennett, Eric Berne, Bobby Short, Cornelius Ryan) (Box 54)
        - May (George Tanham, James Pike, Bill Sands, A.J. Muste, Peter Benenson, Jean La Couture) (Box 54)
        - June (James Cameron, Albert Parry, Margery Hurst, Pierre Rinfret) (Box 54)
        - July (Philip Geyelin, Paul Johnson) (Box 54)
        - August (Orval Faubus, George Wallace, James Meredith, Joel Schumacher, Lois Carlson, James MacGregor Burns) (Box 54)
      - "The Policeman's Lot," March 29 (Box 54)
      - Eleanor Roosevelt Interview from November 23, 1957 (includes publisher correspondence), 1957-1966 (Box 54)
  - 1967
    - Administrative
      - CBS Memos Received (Box 54)
      - CBS Memos Sent (Box 54)
      - Expense Reports (Box 54)
    - Correspondence
      - A-Z, 3 folders (Box 54)
      - Audience Mail, General (Box 54)
    - Personal
      - Invitations (Box 54)
      - Leesburg Properties (Box 54)
      - Peter Wallace Memorial Prize Fund, Yale University (Box 54)
      - Phi Epsilon Pi (Box 55)
      - Resumes (Box 55)
      - Speeches, 2 folders (Box 55)
      - Trainer, Wortham and Company (finances) (Box 55)
      - University of Michigan Sesquicentennial (Box 55)
    - Topical
      - Dissenting Democrats (Box 55)
      - Governors (Box 55)
      - Ideas (Box 55)
      - Ideas for Cronkite Pieces (Box 55)
      - William Manchester's book Death of a President (Box 55)
      - Middle East Crisis (Box 55)
      - National Governors' Conference (Box 55)
      - Politics, General (Box 55)
      - Racial Riots (Box 55)
      - Reports, Miscellaneous (Box 55)
      - Nelson Rockefeller (Box 55)
      - Southern Governors' Conference (Box 55)
      - Strickman Cigarette Filter (Box 55)
      - Vietnam
        - Chieu Hoi Program (Box 55)
        - Committee of Responsibility (Box 55)
        - Deserters (Box 55)
        - Reports from Vietnam (Box 55)
        - Research, 3 folders (Box 55)
      - Warren Report (Box 55)
      - Young Republicans (Box 55)
    - Transcripts/Shows
      - "CBS News The Correspondents Report," January 1, 1966 (Box 55)
      - "Classroom USA: At Issue -- Vietnam," December 7 (Box 55)
      - Face the Nation with John V. Lindsay, November 12 (Box 55)
      - "The Homosexuals," March 7 (Box 55)
      - "How Israel Won the War," July 18 (Box 55)
      - "Middle East Perspective: Can Peace Break Out?" August 23 (Box 55)
      - "Where We Stand in Vietnam," Part 2, November 7 (Box 55)
  - 1968
    - Administrative
      - Expense Reports (Box 56)
      - Memos From Mike Wallace (Box 56)
      - Memos To Mike Wallace (Box 56)
    - Correspondence
      - A-Z, 21 folders (Box 56)
      - Conventions (Box 56)
      - General Mail (Box 56)
      - Hospital Thank-Yous (Box 56)
    - Personal
      - Financial (Box 56)
      - Invitations (Box 56)
    - Topical
      - Black America (Box 56)
      - Campaign '68 (Box 56)
      - Clark, Dr. Kenneth (Box 56)
      - Concerned Negro Republicans of Louisiana (Box 56)
      - Conservative Party (Box 56)
      - Election '68 (Box 56)
      - Governors' Conference, Democrats (Box 56)
      - Governors' Conference, Republicans (Box 56)
      - Humphrey, Hubert (Box 56)
      - Ideas (Box 56)
      - Kennedy, Robert (Box 56)
      - The New Left (Box 56)
      - Polls (Box 56)
      - Primaries, California (Box 56)
      - Primaries, Indiana (Box 56)
      - Primaries, Nebraska (Box 56)
      - Primaries, New Hampshire (Box 56)
      - Primaries, Oregon (Box 56)
      - Primaries, Pennsylvania (Box 56)
      - Primaries, Washington (Box 56)
      - Primaries, Wisconsin (Box 56)
      - Reagan, Ronald (Box 56)
      - Republican National Committee (Box 56)
      - Republican National Convention (Box 56)
      - 60 Minutes Beginnings (Box 56)
      - Wallace, George (Box 56)
    - Transcripts/Shows
      - "The Correspondent's Report," Part II: "The Nation,", January 9, 1968 (Box 56)
  - 1969
    - Administrative
      - Expense Reports (Box 57)
      - Memos From Mike Wallace (Box 57)
      - Memos To Mike Wallace (Box 57)
      - 60 Minutes Memos (Box 57)
      - Visa Application (Box 57)
    - Correspondence
      - A-Z, 20 folders (Box 57)
      - Cables (Box 57)
      - General Mail (Box 57)
    - Personal
      - Awards, 1969-1970 (Box 57)
      - Career Academy (Box 57)
      - Financial (Box 57)
      - Fuller, Jack (regarding tribute in AFTRA Magazine) (Box 57)
      - Invitations (Box 57)
      - Resumes and References (Box 57)
    - Topical
      - Agnew, Spiro (Box 57)
      - Alaska (Box 57)
      - American Deserters in Canada (Box 57)
      - Camp Pendleton (Box 57)
      - Cancer (Box 57)
      - Chemical and Biological Warfare (Box 57)
      - Cohn-Bendit, Danny (Box 57)
      - Concentration Camps (Box 57)
      - DeGaulle and Servan-Schreiber (Box 57)
      - Democratic Party (Box 57)
      - Draft Lawyers (Box 57)
      - Federal Communications Commission (Box 57)
      - Fillmore East and Janis Joplin (Box 57)
      - German Measles (Box 57)
      - German War Babies (Box 57)
      - Governors' Conference (Box 57)
      - Governors, Republican (Box 57)
      - Haynsworth, Judge Clement (Box 58)
      - Hijacking (Box 58)
      - Hunt, H.L. (Box 58)
      - Ideas (Box 58)
      - International Money Game (Box 58)
      - Ireland (Box 58)
      - Israel (Box 58)
      - McCarthy, Eugene (Box 58)
      - Mott, Stewart (Box 58)
      - Muskie, Senator Edmund (Box 58)
      - Nigeria, 3 folders (Box 58)
      - Nixon, Richard M. (Box 58)
      - The Pope and the Pill (Box 58)
      - Prison Assaults (Box 58)
      - Sheen, Bishop Fulton J. (Box 58)
      - Suicides (Box 58)
      - "Tora, Tora, Tora" (Box 58)
      - Vietnam (Box 58)
      - Welfare (Box 58)
      - Zebra Associates (Box 58)
    - Transcripts/Shows
      - "The Correspondent's Report: End of a Decade,", December 26, 1969 (Box 58)
      - "The Heritage of Apollo,", August 26, 1969 (Box 58)
      - Mike Wallace At Large (Box 58)
  - 1970
    - Administrative
      - Expense Reports (Box 58)
      - Memos From Mike Wallace (Box 58)
      - Memos To Mike Wallace (Box 58)
      - Press Coverage (Box 58)
    - Correspondence
      - A-N, 13 folders (Box 58)
      - O-Z, 8 folders (Box 58)
      - General Mail (Box 58)
    - * Personal
      - Invitations, 2 folders (Box 59)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 59)
      - Richard J. Fulton, Inc., Lecture and Artist Bureau (Box 59)
    - Topical
      - Abernathy, Dr. Ralph (Box 59)
      - Alcoholism (Box 59)
      - Ames, Bernard Phillip, 3 folders (Box 59)
      - Arab Commandos (Box 59)
      - B-1 Bomber (Box 59)
      - The Bill of Rights Poll (Box 59)
      - Black Panthers, 2 folders (Box 59)
      - Boxing (Lyle, Frazier, Ali) (Box 59)
      - Buckley, William F. (Box 59)
      - Cable TV (Box 59)
      - Campus Turmoil (Box 59)
      - Castro, Fidel (Box 59)
      - The Child Beaters (Box 59)
      - China's Bomb (Box 59)
      - Classroom USA (Box 59)
      - Cleaver, Eldridge (Box 59)
      - Cornfeld, Bernie (Box 59)
      - Crime in Washington (Box 59)
      - Crum, William J., 3 folders (Box 59)
      - Cuba (Box 59)
      - Dangerous Toys (Box 60)
      - Dayan, Moshe (Box 60)
      - Drugs (Box 60)
      - Egypt, 3 folders (Box 60)
      - Election Night '70 (Box 60)
      - Federal Housing Authority Program (FHA 235) (Box 60)
      - Garbage (Box 60)
      - Germany: Army Relations (Box 60)
      - Heart Disease (Box 60)
      - Hickel, Secretary Walter (Box 60)
      - Hospitals (Box 60)
      - Ideas (Box 60)
      - Marijuana (Box 60)
      - M-48 Torpedo (Box 60)
      - McKissick, Floyd, (Director of Congress on Racial Equality (CORE)) (Box 60)
      - Mitchell, Attorney General John (Box 60)
      - My Lai: McGee versus Hersh Debate (Box 60)
      - National Governors' Conference (Box 60)
      - New Filmmakers (Box 60)
      - Nixon, Richard M. (Box 60)
      - Oil Tankers (Box 60)
      - Pension Plans (Box 60)
      - Pentagon (Box 60)
      - Politics (interviews with Nelson Rockefeller and Arthur Goldberg) (Box 60)
      - Public Opinion Polling (Box 60)
      - Renaissance Drug Rehabilitation Program (Box 60)
      - Stone, W. Clement (PMA--Positive Mental Attitude--Advisor to Nixon) (Box 60)
      - Sweeney, Marine Sergeant Jon M. (charged with desertion in Vietnam) (Box 60)
      - Television News and the Seventies (Box 60)
      - Thurmond, Strom (Box 60)
      - Tobacco Overseas (Box 60)
      - Trudeau, Pierre (Box 61)
      - Underground Press (Box 61)
      - Vietnam, 2 folders (Box 61)
      - War Script (Box 61)
      - White House Tour with Tricia Nixon (Box 61)
    - Transcripts/Shows
      - "Campaign '70: Television and Politics,", October 20, 1970; 2 folders (Box 61)
      - "Face the Nation," Guests: New York Senatorial Candidates, October 25, 1970 (Box 61)
      - Mike Wallace At Large (Box 61)
      - "The National Environment Test,", May 19, 1970 (Box 61)
  - 1971
    - Administrative
      - Expense Reports (Box 61)
      - Memos From Mike Wallace (Box 61)
      - Memos To Mike Wallace (Box 61)
      - 60 Minutes Memos, 1970-1971 (Box 61)
      - 60 Minutes Press Coverage, 1970-1971 (Box 61)
      - 60 Minutes Story Ideas, 1971-1972 (Box 61)
    - Correspondence
      - A-Z, 20 folders (Box 61)
      - Cables (Box 61)
      - General Mail (Box 61)
    - * Personal
      - Invitations (Box 61)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 61)
      - New York Journalism Review (Box 61)
      - The Twentieth Century Fund, Task Force on Governmental Power and Press Freedom, 3 folders (Box 62)
      - University of Michigan Power Center for the Performing Arts (fundraising campaign) (Box 62)
      - University of Texas (archived interviews, request for material) (Box 62)
    - Topical
      - Abortion (Box 62)
      - Agnew, Spiro, 1970-1971; 1973 (Box 62)
      - Americans Living in London (Box 62)
      - Amnesty (Box 62)
      - Amputees Revisited (Box 62)
      - Babies Cry (Box 62)
      - Beard, Dita, 2 folders (Box 62)
      - Berkeley (Box 62)
      - Busing in Washington, DC (Box 62)
      - Cleaver, Eldridge (Box 62)
      - Connally, John (Box 62)
      - Conventions (Box 62)
      - Credit Cards (Box 62)
      - Earthquakes (Box 62)
      - Guantanamo (Box 62)
      - Haiti (Box 62)
      - Hoffa, James (Box 62)
      - Ideas (Box 62)
      - International Longshoremen's Association (Box 63)
      - Irving, Clifford (Howard Hughes) (Box 63)
      - Israel (Box 63)
      - Italian Repatriates (Box 63)
      - Japanese-Americans (Box 63)
      - Japanese Steel (Box 63)
      - Jews Behind the Iron Curtain, 2 folders (Box 63)
      - LBJ Library (dedication, 2 folders) (Box 63)
      - Lindbergh, Charles (Box 63)
      - Lindsay, John V. (Mayor of New York) (Box 63)
      - McCarthy, Eugene (Box 63)
      - McCarthy, John (correspondence regarding murder trial) (Box 63)
      - My Lai (litigation regarding Meadlo and Medina interviews), 1969 (Box 63)
      - No-Fault Insurance (Box 63)
      - North Korea (Box 63)
      - Nuremberg and Vietnam (war crimes, My Lai) (Box 63)
      - Plastic Surgery (Box 63)
      - POW Wives (Box 63)
      - Prisons (Box 63)
      - Property Taxes (Box 63)
      - Prostitution (Box 63)
      - Secrecy (Box 63)
      - "The Selling of the Pentagon" (Box 63)
      - Sinatra, Frank (Box 63)
      - State Fair Project, Dallas (Box 63)
      - Supreme Court Nominees (Box 63)
      - Swedish New Towns (Box 63)
      - Szamek, Pierre, (claim of wrongful dismissal from Newark State College) (Box 63)
      - United Mine Workers (Box 63)
      - United States Postal Service (Box 63)
      - Urban Renewal (Box 63)
      - Vietnam (Box 63)
      - Women's Prisons (Box 63)
    - Transcripts/Shows
      - CBS News Special. "The Correspondents Report." Part I: "The Nation,", December 23, 1971 (Box 63)
      - CBS News Special Report. "The Economy: A New Way to Go,", August 16, 1971 (Box 63)
      - Mike Wallace at Large (Box 63)
  - 1972 with 1970-1973 inter-mixed
    - Administrative
      - Expense Reports (Box 63)
      - Memos From Mike Wallace (Box 63)
      - Memos To Mike Wallace (Box 63)
      - Press Coverage (Box 63)
    - Correspondence
      - A-Z, 22 folders (Box 64)
      - Cables (Box 64)
    - * Personal
      - Book correspondence (Box 64)
      - Convention Invitations (Box 64)
      - Invitations (Box 64)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 64)
      - Resumes (Box 64)
      - Syracuse University (archived materials), 1966-1972 (Box 64)
      - "The Television Reporter" (article for edited book) (Box 64)
    - Topical
      - Amtrak (Box 64)
      - Arbatov, Georgi (USA Institute, Moscow, 2 folders) (Box 64)